<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MindAPI</title><link>https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/</link><description>Recent content on MindAPI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About MindAPI Project</title><link>https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/about/</guid><description>I love mindmaps. They help keep my methodology when doing security research or brainstorming with my collegues. With that in mind I decided to spread some love in the community by creating MindAPI.
Nowadays APIs are part of all modern applications. Creating something that could help the security community to assess an API and at the same time help me by keeping my work organized its a win-win.
MindAPI is a mindmap which combines years of experience in testing API security.</description></item><item><title>References</title><link>https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dsopas.github.io/MindAPI/references/</guid><description>Here you can find a variaty of resources to help you out on the API security path.
Talks / Educational Videos / Recorded Webinars OWASP API Security Top 10 by Erez Yalon &amp;amp; Inon Shkedy Meetups at Checkmarx: An Introduction to API Security Meetups at Checkmarx: API Security Concerns (Part II) Don’t Worry, Be API: Addressing AppSec’s Newest Challenge Common API security pitfalls by Philippe De Ryck API (in)Security TOP 10: Guided tour Top 10 API Bugs (and Where to Find Them) How To Do Recon: API Enumeration Hunting for bugs in GraphQL APIs (Demo) Finding Your Next Bug: GraphQL REST in Peace: Abusing GraphQL to Attack Underlying Infrastructure Hidden in Plain Site: Disclosing Information via Your APIs Bad API, hAPI Hackers!</description></item></channel></rss>